export const questionList = [{
    question: 'John F. Kennedy was assassinated in:',
    ansver: ['New York', 'Austin', 'Dallas', 'Miami'],
    rightAnswer: 'Dallas'
  },
  {
    question: 'World War I began in which year?',
    ansver: ['1923', '1938', '1917', '1914'],
    rightAnswer: '1914'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Hundred Years War was fought between what two countries?',
    ansver: ['Italy and Carthage', 'England and Germany', 'France and England', 'Spain and France'],
    rightAnswer: 'France and England'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 1594 William Shakespeare joined the company of this London theatre.',
    ansver: ['Broadway', 'Oxford University Theatre', 'The Globe', 'The London Palladium'],
    rightAnswer: 'The Globe'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the first Western explorer to reach China?',
    ansver: ['Magellan', 'Cook', 'Marco Polo', 'Sir Francis Drake'],
    rightAnswer: 'Marco Polo'
  },
  {
    question: 'American involvement in the Korean War took place in which decade?',
    ansver: ['1920s', '1950s', '1970s', '1960s'],
    rightAnswer: '1950s'
  },
  {
    question: 'The disease that ravaged and killed a third of Europe`s population in the 14th century is known as:',
    ansver: ['The White Death', 'The Black Plague', 'Smallpox', 'The Bubonic Plague'],
    rightAnswer: 'The Bubonic Plague'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the architect who rebuilt London after the Great Fire of 1666?',
    ansver: ['Sir Christopher Wren', 'Sir Christopher Robin', 'Christopher Columbus', 'I.M. Pei'],
    rightAnswer: 'Sir Christopher Wren'
  },
  {
    question: 'When did Switzerland officially gain its independence?',
    ansver: ['1688', '1708', '1648', '1798'],
    rightAnswer: '1648'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these peoples once ruled Norway?',
    ansver: ['Romans', 'Irish', 'Aztecs', 'Vikings'],
    rightAnswer: 'Vikings'
  },
  {
    question: 'What country was Vasco da Gama from?',
    ansver: ['Spain', 'Germany', 'Italy', 'Portugal'],
    rightAnswer: 'Portugal'
  },
  {
    question: 'In which city was the 1980 Olympic game',
    ansver: ['London', 'Moscow', 'Paris', 'Turin'],
    rightAnswer: 'Moscow'
  },
];